I'm in a seal show today's
goes to a couple in Philadelphia for living in a storage unit undetected for hella long.
Leland Brown Jr. actually ended up throwing it off because he uploaded a video of himself and his partner
living in this storage unit inconspicuously. Now he'd been documenting his journey of homelessness
on TikTok since last March. You know the thing about this though is that like he shouldn't have
to be in this situation, right? Like there's no reason that there should not be abundance of
affordable housing for folks. Like why do we got to live in a storage unit? Like why is there
spaces for property and not spaces for people? Today's letdown goes to bullies because y'all
gonna have to find a new thing to bully the kids about who are showing up in school with
them Bobos. That's right. All you kids who couldn't afford sneakers, baby, there's a new
option. Rent-a-center is now renting.
You